sasha is actually I'll let you know
sasha其实我会告诉你的
because I'm not sure if you're aware
因为我 不确定 你是否知道
sasha is building her own computer yes
sasha正在建造自己的 电脑
yes this is from previous episodes right
是的，这是从以前的剧集开始
it's a multi-part series currently a
它是目前的多部分系列
part for and so do you want to kind of
部分为，所以你想要的那种
explain what where we're at at this
解释我们在 这方面的目标
point we're at the receiving boxes part
我们在接收箱的一部分
so last week we made a shopping list and
所以上周我们制作了购物清单
I immediately went home and I ordered a
我立刻回家了，我点了一个
whole bunch of stuff yeah super fun and
一堆东​​西是的超级有趣和
lots of the boxes have now arrived so
很多的箱子，现在已经到了 这样
that's super cool so what do we whatever
这太酷了所以我们 做 什么
guy I saw the CPU fan right I spot two
我看到CPU风扇的 权利 我发现了两个
CPU itself the motherboard is beautiful
CPU本身的主板很漂亮
it is sharp it really is better than I
它很尖锐它 真的比我好
expected
预期
yeah keyboarding mouse yeah said it
是的键盘鼠标 是啊 说的
that's it yes yeah
是的，是的，是的
other things are sort of on our way so I
其他的东西都在 路上， 所以我
really do want to thank Frank Joseph and
真的要感谢弗兰克 约瑟夫和
Robert who all have donated for the belt
罗伯特都为 腰带 捐 了钱
thank you so much from the absolute
非常感谢你 的绝对
bottom of my heart I cannot wait to
心底我迫不及待地想
share this with Dave and to show him all
与戴夫分享并向他展示一切
that everybody's done from you know
每个人都是从你那里知道的
coming up with the idea of like the
想出的类似想法
whole vision created by you so thank you
你创造了整个愿景所以谢谢你
this is like the first cloud build
这就像第一个云构建
mm-hmm like you viewers you you've
mm-hmm 就像你的观众一样
helped to design the system to pick out
帮助设计了系统来挑选
the parts to to even fund it now and we
现在和我们甚至资助它的部分
appreciate that very very much if you'd
如果你愿意 ，非常感谢
like to pitch in now understand that
喜欢投球现在明白了
this is a wedding gift for Sasha's
这是Sasha's的结婚礼物
husband yeah but you're going to utilize
老公， 是的，但你要利用
it as well your your family computer so
它也是 你的 家庭电脑
so if you'd like to contribute to that
所以，如果你想 贡献 给
as a bit of a wedding gift to the the
作为一个结婚礼物的一点点
happy couple head on over to donate dot
幸福的夫妇头部 到捐赠点
category-five dot TV and you can see
五类点电视 你可以看到
there there's an option to donate
那里有捐赠的选择
specifically do that so a couple of
特别这样做了几个
questions that have arisen since then
从那时起出现的 问题
right that we never thought to bring up
是的，我们从未想过要提起
and I'll explain why because some of the
我会解释为什么因为某些原因
technologies that I didn't bring up are
我没有提到的技术是
things that I
我的一切
use in a desktop computer ever I thought
我想过在台式电脑中使用
well we better ask you and the viewers
我们最好问你和观众
in the forum at cat 5 TV slash CPU 2017
在 cat 5 TV slash CPU 2017 的论坛中
wanted to know do you need Wi-Fi is your
想知道你 需要Wi-Fi是你的
computer going to be connected to
计算机将连接到
wireless how you currently connect your
无线你目前如何连接你的
well okay so I looked a little into it
好吧，所以 我看了一下
right now we're connected into the like
现在我们连 成 类似
the actual physical router like a cable
实际的物理路由器就像一根电缆
going into the computer
进入电脑
yes antastic pellit however okay so we
是的antastic pellit然而好吧所以我们
rent a basement apartment and we have
租一间地下室公寓，我们有
one router that connects like upstairs
一个连接像楼上的路由器
and downstairs like we've all shared
和我们共享的楼下一样
share it with the whole house and right
与 整个房子 和右边 分享
now it's in our apartment but evidently
现在它在我们的公寓但显然
there's connection issues upstairs and
楼上有连接问题
they wanted to move it upstairs so I've
他们想把它搬到楼上， 所以 我
been really encouraging that we don't do
我们 真的很鼓励 我们不这样做
that instead we get one of those things
相反，我们 得到其中一 件事
that just like expands the you know
就像扩展你知道的那样
there's like you know talking about a
就像你知道 谈论一个
little computer yeah so I want to keep
小电脑是啊所以我想 保持
it close so that we don't have to be
它关闭，所以我们 不必
Wi-Fi the answer is yes ish yes could be
Wi-Fi 答案是肯定的 ， 是的，是的
a predicament so Wi-Fi is not as
困境所以Wi-Fi并不像
reliable and it's not as fast exactly so
可靠，并不是那么快
you're gonna have issues with Wi-Fi so
你会遇到Wi-Fi问题
we didn't put a Wi-Fi adapter in it we
我们没有在其中放置Wi-Fi 适配器
didn't buy a motherboard that had
没买的主板是有
built-in Wi-Fi
内置Wi-Fi
we're gonna need it and I wanted to
我们 需要它，我想
suggest that if you do need Wi-Fi just
建议如果你确实需要Wi-Fi
by a USB dongle because that way as
通过USB 加密狗，因为那样
Wi-Fi technology evolves you can just
Wi-Fi技术可以随时发展
pull out that and plug a new one in
拉出来并插入一个新 的
there cheap and it doesn't have to be
有便宜 ， 而且 不必是
part of the build right I'm really
构建的一部分我是真的
usually quite easygoing but I've very
通常很随和，但我 非常
much put my foot down and this whole
我的脚下垂了很多
router movement thing so is there a
路由器运动的东西所以有一个
cable that goes from your router all the
从您的路由器的所有电缆
way up to the apartment upstairs or are
到楼上的公寓或者是
they using Wi-Fi is it weird that I
他们使用Wi-Fi 对我来说很奇怪
don't know it's very strange strange
不知道这是很奇怪 奇怪
I wonder if they're using Wi-Fi they
我想知道他们是否正在使用Wi-Fi
probably are and it's not working it
可能是与它不工作 就
having trouble if they want to reverse
如果 他们想扭转就有麻烦
that so you're the one having trouble so
所以你就是那个遇到 麻烦的人
I think you should have somebody in that
我想你应该有某人在
can run what's called a network drop an
可以运行所谓的网络丢弃
Ethernet cable that goes up through the
以太网电缆通过
walls or through the floor okay to the
墙壁或通过地板没关系
router and then extends that to what's
路由器，然后将其扩展到什么
called a switch so you have the router
称为交换机，所以你有路由器
and then a big long cable going down to
再大的长电缆下降到
your apartment or vice versa and then a
你的公寓，反之亦然 ，然后一个
switch on the other end which turns that
转动 另一端 转动它
one cable into five ports right and you
一根电缆连接到五个端口 和你
can network them all together but keep
可以将 它们 联网 在一起但 保持不变
in mind even the way that you're doing
记住你正在做的事情
this the way that you have your computer
这就是 你拥有计算机的方式
connecting to a network with the people
与人们连接到网络
upstairs if they got a virus if they got
如果他们得到了病毒，他们会在楼上
ransomware your computer is susceptible
勒索软件你的电脑容易受到攻击
oh okay because you're on the same
哦， 好吧，因为你是 一样的
what's called a local area network it's
什么叫做局域网
a computer network all of them can talk
一个计算机网络，他们都可以说话
to each other like your office all the
对方 喜欢你 办公室里的
computers can access each other's files
计算机可以访问彼此的文件
and communicate with one another so
并且彼此通信，从而
you're gonna be you're not going to be a
你会成为一个不会成为你的人
threat to them because you're installing
因为你正在安装而对他们构成威胁
Linux on your computer mm-hmm
Linux上的电脑 mm-hmm
however they are a threat to you because
但是它们对你构成威胁，因为
I would imagine that they probably have
我想他们可能有
Microsoft Windows and so if you have
如果你有 Microsoft Windows 等等
files on your computer which you will
您将在计算机上的文件
and if they are shared in such a way
如果他们以这种方式分享
that you can access them from your
你可以 从 你的 访问它们
laptop and you can access them from your
笔记本电脑，你可以从你的
other devices well guess what so can
其他设备很好地猜测是什么
they
他们
okay so your block that's the same
好的，所以你的块是一样的
network you're connected to the very
网络你连接到 了
same network okay and I'm guessing they
同样的网络 没关系，我猜它们
don't have the infrastructure to add a
没有基础设施来添加
second subnet with not not likely so so
第二个子网不太可能如此
understand the that that is the
明白那就是了
susceptibility oh yeah you might want to
易受伤害哦，是的，你可能想要
look into something else I don't know
看看我不知道的其他事情
yeah probably
是的，可能
do you concur absolutely all the time
你完全同意所有的 时间
[Laughter]
[笑声]
risk though okay and ransomware is the
风险虽然好，勒索软件就是
biggest concern okay because they go out
最大的担心没关系 ，因为他们走出去
through the network and look for other
通过网络 寻找其他
computers and encrypt their files right
计算机和 右 加密他们的文件
it wouldn't actually be like the
它实际上不会像
upstairs neighbor trying anything it
楼上的邻居试了一下它
would be a ransom well it could be I
这将是一笔赎金，它可能是我
mean whatever if the Wi-Fi was open your
无论如何Wi-Fi打开你的意思
Wi-Fi reaches like two kilometers yeah
Wi-Fi达到两公里是的
like a mile and so anyone who can
像一英里，所以任何人都可以
compromise the because I know it sounds
妥协，因为我知道这听起来
like you probably know a lot about your
就像你 可能对你的了解很多
setup and that you have in place
设置 ，你已经到位
kostik yeah and so somebody within like
kostik耶，所以有人喜欢
a a mile of that router could connect
一英里的 路由器可以连接
into the Wi-Fi hypothetically and still
假设和静止地进入Wi-Fi
access things and all that cancer so
获取所有癌症和所有癌症
there's there's some condense acuity yes
有一些 浓缩的敏锐度是的
okay
好的
[Music]
[音乐]